https://www.scienceforums.net/privacy/

Privacy Policy
To facilitate normal operation and administration of the forum, ScienceForums.net keeps the IP addresses and email addresses used by forum members, as well as whatever personal information they choose to enter in their member profile. Member profiles are public and are not protected by this policy.
ScienceForums.net staff will neither release email or IP addresses, nor read or make public private messages, unless one or more of the following conditions applies:
ScienceForums.net is ordered to do so by a court of law or required to do so by law
Explicit consent is given by the users in question
The data is necessary to protect ScienceForums.net or its staff from legal action
The data is necessary to aid legal or administrative action wherein the user has violated ScienceForums.net policy, the policy of their Internet Service Provider, or applicable law.
ScienceForums.net will never release or sell private information to other companies or organizations except in the above cases.
Our Commitment to Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
Cookies
This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties.
Third Parties
Google Analytics
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.
Privacy Policy
Spam Defense
The IPS Spam Defense Service passes the email address and IP address of the registering member to the service to determine the likelihood a registering account is a spam source.
Privacy Policy
reCAPTCHA V2
This site uses a CAPTCHA to ensure humans are performing certain actions. The CAPTCHA provider may set a session cookie and get information about your internet browser and device accessing this website.
Privacy Policy
All Activity
Home
Privacy Policy
Important Information
We have placed cookies on your device to help make this website better. You can adjust your cookie settings, otherwise we'll assume you're okay to continue.
I accept
